You know she's such a beautiful girl she loves to get
response but now I want to appeal to the
emotional notes of all our friends
sitting especially for every buddy who wants to bring that
feeling of coming to Thailand
to coming to Bangkok Pattaya single if you want that
feeling to come then I
need that energy I know your partners your family is with
you but once we should show them what the josh is how the
josh my saaak
show the josh together one to one too they come
on
amazing oh this to Reva has started right now she is
running fast at least ah okay you have done this but I
think my side was better
give them a demo once again guy on the counter one
to one to you
[applause] thank you so much
here we were taking this test
because we have just learnt the
flight has been cancelled back to India so
you all will go back at the speed of a train the more you clap the
train will speed up  It will
go towards history with great force, right? Just kidding
and use your energy and right now, one more little thing we need to get them
to create a
memory. Okay, so how do we do that? Everyone will have
their own cell phones. Everyone has them. The
ladies are the first to reach in, there are
camera apps too. And now our favorite thing we
love to do, and we never miss, never miss, we took out
our fans. We were taking a lot of selfies.
Now there will be a public selfie, in
which you are requested to
take a selfie in which you can convince everyone sitting with you near your table.
When you are taking a selfie, make sure that every person behind you
makes a heart in your selfie and then when your turn comes,
you also make a heart in their selfie. Let's see, you can do this. Come and at as many
people as you can in one selfie on your
mobile. This evening is going to be very memorable. You will
remember looking at the selfie later.
[Music]
Of
course, you should do it for yourselves and for those who are sitting around you,
look at the action right, take it out, take it out,
so look at this, only one person on the table
selfie, this is not your responsibility,
everyone will take a selfie and everyone will participate in it, yes let me and all
my friends sitting behind, come and stand and take a selfie after seeing it, this is a
beautiful place, because you know what a
request I have from ICICI Loba Sir, you can
kindly wake up in front but because we want you to take a
selfie with all of our
partners behind us because this is one
huge ICICI Lo family, so sir, I
request you to come here in front and do it in front of the stage, I think the
stage will be better, better, please, please can we have
you up on stage, then we will take such a selfie in
which everyone behind you here will give you
hearts, okay, everyone will give you hearts,
money to you people.  You are
working so hard, so much, let's now share some love with everyone, absolutely.
Now put down your phones. It's
time to put down the phones and just make a cute
little heart. Yes, Dil Se Dil Tak, and we have our buses here. Give it up to everyone.
One of them. You can just point out the camera. Take a
selfie and let's all of you have a good ear.
[Applause]
[Music]
Sir, you have done it. All your
performers who had commented will come to
Pattaya this time. Next year also, these
people will come. You have proved it in the selfie.
You guys are very thankful. Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
Like we were saying in the beginning, what makes
us stronger and what makes us better is
the fact that we are a family. We got that click
activity done. So you see the difference,
right when we are alone, we are not so strong. We are
strong, not together. And
we love the spirit of this family, everyone and all of
us.  We know that a family
progresses beautifully only when the management of that family is
good.
Just like some
pillars are needed to establish any building, similarly some pillars are needed to
run any organization.
Some such people who
act as pillars of strength,
inspire us, motivate us. Today we start this program
by inviting on
stage one such leader, everyone who loves, has a back,
loves, inspires us, motivates us. I take this
opportunity of requesting our
head agency SME and you to join us.
With applause, let's
welcome Gooding Sir.